This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hat crew,
Rufy is headed to Navy Headquarters in order to rescue his brother from death.
However, there are only three hours left before the public execution of Port Castile Ace.
Ticking down to the time of battle!
The Navy's strongest lineup in position!
stand up.
b
Transcription by CastingWords
CastingWords